

# David Simon

Date of birth: 05/02/1997

**Nationality:** Macedonian/citizen of the Republic of North Macedonia

Gender: Male

#### CONTACT



Sremski Front 23-9, null 2000 Shtip, North Macedonia



simond997@gmail.com



(+389) 78475554

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-simon1/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-simon1/</a>

Whatsapp Messenger: +3897847 5554

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a flexible and experienced office administrator with excellent time management skills. I am a good communicator with proven inter personal skills and am used to working in a teams being capable of using own initiative. I am skilled In dealing with problems in a resourceful manner and negotiating to achieve beneficial agreement. I am always enthusiastic to learn and undertake new challenges

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

03/2022 - 06/2022 - Shtip, North Macedonia

### International Training Consultant

### **LEORON** Institute

Present, promote and sell products/services using solid arguments to existing and prospective customers

Perform cost-benefit and needs analysis of existing/potential customers to meet their needs

Establish, develop and maintain positive business and customer relationships Reach out to customer leads through cold calling

Expedite the resolution of customer problems and complaints to maximize satisfaction

Coordinate sales effort with team members and other departments

Analyze the territory/market's potential, track sales and status reports

Supply management with reports on customer needs, problems, interests, competitive activities, and potential for new products and services.

Keep abreast of best practices and promotional trends

Technology and Development / <u>leoron.com</u> / Indigo Icon Tower - Office Dubai, United Arab Emirates . امارة دسيّ - 1208

11/2021 - 02/2022 - Shtip, North Macedonia

### Compliance Representative

Superior Dispatch Service / A2B Cargo Logistics Inc.

Given opportunity to build the Compliance Representative as a new position, part of Accounting, from the very beginning.

Making a project and analysis with new policies complied with the Managers.

Ensure all employees are educated on the latest regulations and processes.

Resolve driver's concerns about legal compliance.

Setting up new Carriers in Company's system and reviewing their Documentation

Monitoring old and new Carriers on Federal web sites and Carrier411.

Making a phone calls with Carriers in order to help them for proceeding the necessary documentation

Making a phone calls with Insurance Companies in order to verify Carrier's Insurance Policies.

Writing Weekly and Monthly Reports to the Representatives of the company, Directors and Managers, in order to keep them updated about the progress of Compliance department

Accounting / <a href="http://a2b-cargo.com/">http://a2b-cargo.com/</a> / 636 S River Rd, st. 100-E, 60016, Des Plaines, United States

08/2021 - 11/2021 - Shtip, North Macedonia

#### Track & Trace

Superior Dispatch Service / A2B Cargo Logistics Inc.

Tracking of vehicles locations by GPS system.

Ensuring strict compliance with company regulations by drivers.

Identifying on-road exceptions and taking immediate remedial action.

Co-ordinating and responding to emergency situations.

Making a phone calls with the drivers and the customer on a daily basis Resolving driver's issues and reacting on difficult situation immediate Writing daily reports to the customers, shippers, store and warehouse management.

Operations / http://a2b-cargo.com/ / 636 S River Rd, st. 100-E, 60016, Des Plaines, IL, United States

06/2021 - 08/2021 - Shtip, North Macedonia

### Recruiter

### Superior Dispatch Service / KSM Carrier Group

Source and recruit candidates by using databases, social media etc

Assess applicants relevant trucking skills, experience and aptitudes

Onboard new employees in order to become fully integrated

Monitor and apply HR recruiting best practices

Act as a point of contact and build influential candidate relationships during the selection process

Making a phone calls with protentional candidates in order to promote them the company's offers, requirements and conditions, and helping them to proceed the necessary documentation before getting them onboard.

HR / <a href="https://ksmcarriergroup.com">https://ksmcarriergroup.com</a> / 2011 Griffith Blvd Suite B, 46319, Griffith, IN, United States

12/2018 - 03/2019 - Shtip, North Macedonia

### **Junior Operator**

Mozzart Bet

Work in a sport bet company as a computer and check out operator Gained skills with Amadeus program.

Gained experience working with slots machines and their daily calculation and treasury reports.

Gained experience with making daily reports and calculations.

Other service activities / <a href="https://www.mozzartbet.mk">https://www.mozzartbet.mk</a> / Vancho Prkje 28, 2000, Shtip, North Macedonia

### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

10/2015 - CURRENT - Shtip, North Macedonia

### Geological engineer - Hydrologist

University of 'Goce Delchev'

### Field(s) of study

Engineering

EQF level 7 | https://www.ugd.edu.mk/

**09/2011 - 05/2015** - Shtip, North Macedonia

### High School Diploma

Municipal High School 'Slavcho Stojmenski'

#### Field(s) of study

Generic programmes and qualifications

EQF level 6 http://slavcostojmenski.edu.mk/

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Macedonian

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

German

<b>Reading</b> A1	Spoken production A1	<b>Spoken</b> interaction A1	<b>Writing</b> A1
<b>Reading</b> B2	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	<b>Writing</b> B2
	A1 Reading	A1 production A1  Reading Spoken	A1 production interaction A1 A1  Reading Spoken Spoken B2 production interaction

### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Amadeus Ticketing Software / Microsoft/Microsoft Office / Adobe Acrobat PRO / Google Spreadsheet / Transportpro System / GPS TRUCK / DAT / Truckstop

#### RECOMMENDATIONS

Dejan Gjoshevski – HR Manager – <u>hr@superiordispatchservice.com</u> Additional recommendations available by my previous company

Gentiana Peza – Lead HR Specialist – <u>gentiana.peza@leoron.com</u> Additional recommendations available by my previous company

### COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

## • Communication and interpersonal skills

Acquired and upgraded knowledge of foreign languages, English and German.

Acquired communication skills in relation to customers, drivers, clients, shippers, Insurance companies, managers, directors.

Writing an official e-mails as an important skill due to grammatical correctness for the image of the Company.

Skills of Tracking the Trucks in real time on GPS application.

Skills of resolving Truck driver issues and difficult situation on time / immediate.

Acquired Cold Calling skills as Sales Person / Consultant promoting and offering products and services.

Acquired skills of making presentations, different kind of reports (daily, monthly, treasury reports) making projects and establishing new position in the company

Acquired skills of different IT - Web Platforms and Programs.

### **VOLUNTEERING**

2013 - 2014

### **Event assistant / Pop Music Festival 'Makfest'**

Shtip

Part of the professional team with assigned tasks for successful organization and the best hospitality of all music stars, part of the competition.

Part of the organizing team for the calendar years 2013 and 2014.

http://www.makfest.mk/